Sam B. Hall, Jr. Papers, Inclusive: 1943-2005, undated Bulk: 1976-1985
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Photographs, Albums, and Scrapbooks, 1943-2001, undated; 14
  - Albums and Scrapbooks, 1950-2001, undated; 2
    - EVENTS, Unidentified Dinner, Marshall, TX, undated (Box 537, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations on Nomination as Federal Judge, 1985 (Box 537, Folder 2)
    - Congratulations on Judges Portrait Presentation in Marshall, TX, 1991 November 15 (Box 537, Folder 3)
    - Judges Portrait Hanging, undated (Box 538, Folder 1)
    - Marshall-Harrison County Salute Judge Sam B. Hall, Jr. Dinner, undated (Box 538, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings, Hall’s Involvement in Civic Organizations, 1950-1956 (Box 538, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings and Photographs Prepared by Marguerite Ratcliff, 1976-1989 (Box 539, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings, Photographs, and Other Items Prepared by Marguerite Ratcliff, 1976-1991 (Box 540, Folder 1)
    - Ronald Reagan Notes and Correspondence to Hall, 1981-1985 (Box 540, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook of News Clippings, Photographs, and Other Items Prepared by Marguerite Ratcliff, 1976-1978 (Box 541, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook Documenting Evacuations of Japanese Americans during World War II, 1984 (Box 541, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook for Congressional Delegation Trip to Southeast Asia (Vietnam) and Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, undated (Box 542, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1991 (Box 542, Folder 2)